At our darkest time, a moment will come that will define who we are.
Natural Selection is a drama, crime film directed by Chad L. Scheifele.
Tyler is a young man who is desperately seeking direction
from a world that seems to have abandoned him.
Searching for answers he looks to his new friend Indrid
who appears to have it all figured out.
Tyler Evans, played by Mason Dye.
Indrid Wardin, played by Ryan Munzert.
Mr. Stevenson, played by Anthony Michael Hall.
Paige Thomas, played by Katherine McNamara.
Laura, played by Amy Carlson.
Angela Wardin (as Esther Zyskind), played by Esther Zynn.
Natural Selection is a 2016 American crime thriller
drama film written and directed by Chad L.
Scheifele (in his feature directorial debut), based on
his 2009 short film of the same name.
It stars Mason Dye, Katherine McNamara, Anthony Michael
Hall, Amy Carlson, and Ryan Munzert.
It follows a shy teenager who, after moving to a new town with his alcoholic mother, is
targeted by bullies at his new high school and drawn into a violent plan.
The film was released in select theaters and on VOD and
iTunes on August 26, 2016, by ITN Distribution.
It received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of high school, manipulation, bullying, bully, murder.
The tone is emotional.